Seven weeks have passed since we set sail from Enroth.
Slaves freed from our skirmishes with Regnan fleets talk of the turmoil in Arathia.
I suspect their stories are true, but I
must see the evidence with my own eyes.
The ocean tides were kind enough to bury the fallen on its shores.
However, the smoking ruins of Cloudfire greeted us with nothing but destruction and a stench of death.
With no survivors, only the battlefield
could tell me what happened here.
Despite the breath of devastation, the presence of Minotaurs suggests a raiding party.
However, the ranks were too well organized.
This is the work of the Dungeon Overlords.
Evidently, the wizards were prepared, but overrun nevertheless.
These atrocities rend my heart and fuel my anger.
Arathia's banner must be respected, never disgraced.
I think of my beloved Rowand
and my son Nikolai and how much
further this war will carry me
from them, but my duty is clear.
My father's kingdom must survive.
Arathia must not fall to its enemies.